Bui Duc Chung

Hoang Mai, Ha Noi chungbd90@gmail.com 0989 313 062

SUMMARY

I am constantly striving to gain more knowledge and experiences to improve my technical as well as soft skills. I see this as crucial for reaching my goals in less time and with lower effort to be more effective.

I love football and marathon.

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer, PTI Insurance Corporation,

February 2019 - Present

PTI Claim

- Descriptions: Save 50% processing time in customer's claim and shorten the process of claim guarantee in 2 hours by mobile solution.
- Main Responsibilities:
 - Build base project and components on Flutter: Text Field, Date Picker, Drop List, Popup, Dialog.
 - Integrate Auto Distribution by Fastlane tools to release regularly new builds (Android and iOS) to QC team
 - Construct elegant and effective source code, through self motivation and collaboration with other engineering resources and product team to troubleshoot and make design changes accordingly
- Technologies used:
 - Camera, Photo
 - Location on background
 - Google Map SDK
 - Push Notification: Onesignal
 - API Restfull, Socket IO
 - Local Storage: Key-Value, SQLite.

PTI Portal

- Descriptions: the tools for internal staff to view, examine insurance order and receive notification when having new one and examining with another
- Main Responsibilities:
 - Using own base components and charts in statistical function for sellers: income, bonus and etc
- PTI Insurance on App Store /PTI Insurance on Play Store

Assistant Product Manager, PTI Insurance Corporation,

April 2021 - July 2021

- Be a project manage role with outsourcing partners: receive requirements, assign works for team member, solve disputes and report project timeline to Division Director.
- Study and change the work process for fixing bugs and changing requirements from business faster.

iOS Developer and Team Lead, BA GPS, August 2017 - February 2019

- Analyze product requirements and specifications to create, communicate, and implement the technical design.
- Guide, support the member of the team to do their task; Fix serious bugs.

- Develop the application on mobile and give the digital solutions for traditional transport companies.
- Binh Anh Electronic Co., Ltd

iOS Developer

Vccorp JSC

May 2016 - August 2017

• Redesign UI and maintain features for a digital wallet in second phase. Wepay

iOS Leader Regen Solution

August 2015 - October 2016

- Develop social applications for public health: Social network about donating blood.
- Analyze the mobile architecture for projects, develop the applications from clients, and provide solutions to their problems.

iOS Developer

OSD - CMC Software Solution June 2014 - July 2015

- Join outsourcing project with responsibility:
 - Fixing issues from client.
 - Developing new functions and UIs.

C/C++ Developer

A.N.LAB JSC

January 2013 - April 2014

- Research and offer a solution for Japanese customer requirement.
- Built Image Processing core for mobile desktop devices by C/C++.

Research topics: Preprocessing, Motion tracking, Matching object.

COMPUTER SKILLS

My Github: Chung Bui

Programming Languages: C, C++, Objective-C, Swift, Python, Golang, Java Script and Dart

Dev tools: Git, Docker, Github, GitLab, Figma, Notion, Jira, VS Code, Vim, Zsh, Bash.

Highlight:

- Train & build Flutter team from zero
- Build project-core, project-template, write documentation
- Recruitment support

LANGUAGES

English

Vietnamese

Limited working proficiency

Native

EDUCATION

The Degree of Engineer in Applied Mathematics and Informatics,

School of Applied Mathematics and Informatics,

Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Hanoi, Vietnam, 2008 - 2013

GPA: 2.5/4

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Sense of responsibility and carefulness in all the works done are my greatest strengths.

ACTIVITY

Participated in A.N Lab Open day contest 2012.

HOBBIES

Running, playing football, traveling, and join English clubs.